{
    "subject": "Archduke_Ferdinand_Karl_Viktor_of_Austria-Este",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Archduchess_Elisabeth_Franziska_of_Austria",
    "human_readable": "Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor of Austria-Este is married to Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9861095547676086,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor of Austria-Este and Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9853206276893616,
            "question": "Who was Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor of Austria-Este married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9823495745658875,
            "question": "To whom was Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9734317064285278,
            "question": "What is the name of Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor of Austria-Este's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.95915287733078,
            "question": "Were Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor and Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska related?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9573625922203064,
            "question": "Who was Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.947317361831665,
            "question": "What was the name of Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9165161848068237,
            "question": "What can we infer about the social standing of Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor of Austria-Este and Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria based on their titles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8850067257881165,
            "question": "Did Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor of Austria-Este have any other wives?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8818164467811584,
            "question": "Was Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor of Austria-Este single?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor of Austria-Este is married to Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria.",
            "html": "yago_26171_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor of Austria-Este have any other wives?",
            "html": "yago_26171_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What can we infer about the social standing of Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor of Austria-Este and Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria based on their titles?",
            "html": "yago_26171_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria?",
            "html": "yago_26171_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26171_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26171_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26171_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26171_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26171_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26171_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26171_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26171_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26171_89.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_26171_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents clearly state that Ferdinand Karl Viktor married Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because all four documents mention that Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor of Austria-Este was indeed married to Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria, with the marriage date specified as December 4, 1846."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Ferdinand married Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria, daughter of Archduke Josef Anton of Austria and his third wife Duchess Maria Dorothea of W\u00fcrttemberg on 4 December 1846 in the Sch\u00f6nbrunn Palace in Vienna.\" This confirms that Archduke Ferdinand Karl Viktor of Austria-Este is indeed married to Archduchess Elisabeth Franziska of Austria."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}